readyportal.net 2009-11-23

# ReadyPortal: Privacy Policy

Protecting your privacy is important to ReadyPortal.com We have created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to keep your personal information confidential. By ensuring that you are aware of and understand Red Dog's Customer Privacy Policy, we can provide you with better service. Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information.

**Why and How We Collect Personal Information**  
Red Dog collects and uses your personal information to provide outstanding customer service and convenient access to our products and services. In addition, we use your personal information to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and other information we think you would like to hear about. From time to time, we may also use your personal information to contact you to participate in a market research survey, so that we can measure customer satisfaction and develop better products.

**IP Addresses**  
We may use your IP address (not your e-mail address) to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Web Site, or to gather broad demographic information.

**User Registration**  
You may choose to fill out a registration form on our Web site with contact information that we may need. This information is used to send you requested information or products, to contact you with other product information, news or promotions, and to learn more about our Web visitors. You may choose not to receive any further information from us any time.

**Online Surveys**  
From time to time, we may conduct online surveys. Our surveys may ask you for demographic information, such as ZIP code or your industry sector. If the online survey collects contact data, we may use that data to send you additional information only if we specifically asked for your permission in the survey. You are free to opt-out of receiving future mailings at any time for more details, check out the Choice/Opt-Out section below.

**Cookies**  
We may use cookies to enhance the user experience and deliver personalized content. Cookies help us to deliver information specific to your interests, to save your having to re-enter your password each time you visit our site, or to keep track of your shopping cart. Cookies also allow us to better analyze our site traffic patterns so that we can bolster our Web offering.

**Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. ReadyPortal.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Web sites. Please refer to the policies of the respective site.
